{
    "id": "fdabfa88f00242209cac45471861fdc8",
    "title": "Used To And Be Used To",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c041ef7d04b241589007a0bf26eca442",
            "title": "Used To And Be Used To",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I am not used to ............................. late hours.",
                    "description": "The to in be used to is a preposition. We use ing forms after prepositions. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "work",
                        "working",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He used to ............................. a lot.",
                    "description": "We use an infinitive after used to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "smoke",
                        "smoking",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I used to ………………………… pop music, but now I don’t.",
                    "description": "We use an infinitive after used to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "hate",
                        "hating",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "When we were children, we used to ………………………… a lot of time playing hide and seek.",
                    "description": "We use an infinitive after used to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "spend",
                        "spending"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………………… be afraid of spiders.",
                    "description": "We use used to to talk about things that happened at an earlier stage of our life.",
                    "answers": [
                        "used to",
                        "am used to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You used not to eat meat, ………………………….?",
                    "description": "Used is not used in questions tags. Instead we use did.",
                    "answers": [
                        "used you",
                        "didn't you",
                        "did you"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "When I was in Mumbai, I ………………………….. visit my grandparents every month.",
                    "description": "We use used to to talk about things that happened at an earlier stage of our life.",
                    "answers": [
                        "used to",
                        "was used to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………… my grandparents twice last month.",
                    "description": "We do not use used to to simply say how many times something happened.",
                    "answers": [
                        "visited",
                        "used to visit",
                        "was used to visiting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………………………….  a big car, but now I do.",
                    "description": "We use didn’t use to to talk about something we hadn’t done in the past.",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't use to drive",
                        "wasn't used to driving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………………………… a big car so I was scared.",
                    "description": "If you aren’t used to doing something, it is not familiar to you.",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't use to drive",
                        "wasn't used to driving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It took me quite some time to get used to ………………………….. in a big city.",
                    "description": "We use an ing form after get used to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "live",
                        "living"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Little by little, she …………………………….. her new family.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "used to",
                        "became used to",
                        "got used to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}